http://www.heidelbergcement.com/en/social-privacy-statement

How Cement Is Made
Group Areas + CountriesWestern and Southern EuropeBeneluxFranceGermanyItalySpainUnited KingdomNorthern and Eastern Europe-Central AsiaAlbaniaBaltic StatesBulgariaBosnia and HerzegovinaCroatiaCzechiaDenmarkGeorgiaGreeceHungaryIcelandKazakhstanNorwayPolandRomaniaRussiaSlovakiaSwedenNorth AmericaCanadaUSAAsia-PacificAustraliaBangladeshBruneiChinaIndiaIndonesiaMalaysiaSingaporeThailandAfrica-Eastern Mediterranean BasinEgyptIsraelMoroccoSub-Saharan AfricaTurkeyGroup Services/Trade
Group Services/Trade
Corporate GovernanceDeclaration of Corporate GovernanceArticles of AssociationRemuneration ReportManagers' TransactionsRules of Procedure for the Supervisory BoardManaging BoardDr. Dominik von AchtenDr. Lorenz N‰gerKevin GluskieHakan GurdalErnest JelitoJon MorrishChris WardSupervisory BoardSupplier + Purchasing Information
Supplier Sustainability Initiative
History
History Website (in German)
Reference Projects
HeidelbergCement
54,000 Employees3,000 Locations>50 Countries
Sustainability StrategyResponsible Management
Responsible Management
Sustainability Commitments 2030
Sustainability Report
Sustainability Report
Ratings + Rankings
Ratings and Rankings
Sustainability Strategy
EnvironmentEnergy + Climate ProtectionAlternative Raw Materials + Fuels
Alternative Raw Materials and Fuels
Local Environmental Impacts
Local Environmental Impacts
Biodiversity + Land Use
Biodiversity and Land Use
Sustainable Construction
Sustainable Construction
Quarry Life Award
Sustainability News
Stay informed and subscribe to the Sustainability Newsletter
Energy and Climate Protection
Energy and Climate Protection
Sustainability Report
ShareInvestment HighlightsShare Price CenterEarnings per shareDividendAnalyst EstimatesShareholder StructureNotifications of Voting RightsMandatory Publications
Share Price Center
Bonds + RatingRatingCommercial Paper ProgrammeDebt Maturity ProfileEuro Bonds
Bonds and Rating
Events + PublicationsFinancial CalendarQuarterly Reporting
Quarterly Reporting
Annual General Meeting
Annual General Meeting 2020
Road Shows + Conferences
Road Shows and Conferences
Capital Markets Day
Capital Markets Day 2020
Ad Hoc Notifications
Q3 2020 Results
Key Financial DataBalance SheetIncome StatementStatement of Comprehensive IncomeStatement of Cash FlowsSegment ReportingStatement of Changes in Equity
Key Financial Data
Contacts
Q3 2020 Results
Capital Markets Day 2020
Press ReleasesPress PhotosHeidelbergCement BlogNewsletter SubscriptionPress Contact Person
HeidelbergCement Blog
Reference Projects
Working at HeidelbergCementCompany OverviewCorporate CultureWork-Life BalanceDiversity + Talent ManagementEmployees in Dialogue
Employees in Dialogue
Corporate Social ResponsibilityStudentsInternships
Internships
Working Students
Working Students
Final Thesis
Final Thesis
GraduatesExecutive Assistant Program
Executive Assistant Program
Trainee ProgramsFinance, Accounting + ControllingHuman ResourcesTechnologySalesDirect Hiring Following Graduation
Direct Hiring Following Grad.
Professionals
Looking for a next step?
Jobs for Professionals
News + EventsJob Offers
Latest News
Our Job Offers
Home© HeidelbergCement AGSocial Privacy Statement
Share this page
Social Privacy Statement
Legal Notice, Privacy Policy and Netiquette for the Social Media Presence†of HeidelbergCement AGThe following Legal Notice and the following Privacy Policy apply to the presence of HeidelbergCement AG in the following social media and third-party platforms:TwitterLinkedInInstagramSlideShareYouTubeXINGThese are hereinafter collectively referred to as "social media".Unless expressly designated otherwise, our presence in social media is generally referred to as "social media presence" below.The following declaration concerning the processing of personal data only refers to the processing by HeidelbergCement AG itself. Additionally, the providers of the listed social media process personal data of both registered users and of unregistered visitors to their websites. As they are directly responsible for these, the user or visitor should inform himself or herself directly on providersí websites about the processing of his or her personal data.Go to Privacy PolicyGo†to NetiquetteLegal NoticeHeidelbergCement AGBerliner Straﬂe 669120 HeidelbergGermanyPhone: +49 6221 481-0Fax: +49 6221 481-13217info@heidelbergcement.comRegistered with the Mannheim district court ('Amtsgericht').Registration No.: HRB 330082VAT No.: DE143455653Represented by the Managing BoardDr. Dominik von Achten, ChairmanDr. Lorenz N‰ger, Deputy ChairmanKevin GluskieHakan GurdalErnest JelitoJon MorrishChris WardChairman of the Supervisory Board: Fritz-J¸rgen HeckmannResponsible for the content in the meaning of Section 55 of the German Broadcasting Treaty (RStV)Group Communication & Investor Relations, HeidelbergCement, GermanyChristoph BeumelburgDirector Group Communication & Investor RelationsBerliner Straﬂe 669120†HeidelbergGermanyPrivacy PolicyResponsible for the collection of data in connection with the above-mentioned social media presence of HeidelbergCement AG ("controller"):HeidelbergCement AG (hereinafter referred to as "we", "us", "our")Represented by the Management BoardDr. Dominik von Achten, ChairmanDr. Lorenz N‰ger, Deputy ChairmanKevin GluskieHakan GurdalErnest JelitoJon MorrishChris WardBerliner Straﬂe 669120 HeidelbergPhone: +49 6221 481-0Fax: +49 6221 481-13217info@heidelbergcement.comThe data protection officer of HeidelbergCement AG can be reached at:Berliner Straﬂe 669120 Heidelbergdatenschutz@heidelbergcement.comPhone: +49 6221-481-39603Collection and Processing of DataWe collect and process personal data within the scope of the use of our social media presence by the data subjects. These data are processed according to the provisions of the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), the German Federal Data Protection Act (BDSG) and the German Telemedia Act (TMG). "Personal data" are all information that refers to an identified or identifiable natural person. In the following, we explain in detail which data we collect and how and on what legal basis we do so. Moreover, we explain which rights you have and for how long your data are stored.Processing of Your Personal Data in the Context of ContactsWhen you provide us with personal data by establishing contact, e.g. by e-mail or by means of a direct message in the social media, we process your data according to point (b) of Art. 6 (1) sentence 1 GDPR for the purpose of performing the contract or in order to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract or pursuant to point (f) of Art. 6 (1) sentence 1 GDPR on the basis of our legitimate interest in answering your request. In this context, we process the data that you directly make available to us via your request. In the social media, these data comprise your user name, your photograph and the message that you send us. Moreover, we may visit your public profile and save data from your profile if necessary for the above-mentioned purposes.Processing of User Data and Statistical Dataa) Processing of Personal DataIn all our social media presences, we receive notifications as to whether users of the social media "Like" our submissions, find them interesting,†share, recommend or comment them, etc. (depending on the function of the social media). Furthermore, we can see a list of our followers or subscribers. On XING, we can see a list of the visitors to our social media presence on this platform. We can also see when you rate our company, insofar as the rating is linked to the respective social media presence.b) Processing of Statistical DataWe also receive statistical analyses of the use of our social media presence from all social media providers. Apart from the information mentioned in 3. a), this merely comprises anonymised data, e.g. (depending on the provider) demographic data, an anonymised analysis of the interaction and reach of our social media presence and submissions, anonymised information such as language, interests and devices used by our users.c) Processing of Data for Advertising Purposes, Creation of Usage Profiles by the Social Media ProvidersThe data specified under a) and b) can also be processed for market research and advertising purposes. For example, this takes place when we publish ads in the respective social media. However, the data are processed by the respective providers. Please also note that usage profiles may be created from your usage behaviour. In turn, these usage profiles can be used e.g. to publish ads in and outside the platforms that might suit your interests. More information on this is available from the respective social media providers.d) Legal Basis for the Processing of DataThe processing of the data mentioned under a) to c) takes place pursuant to point (f) of Art. 6 (1) sentence 1 GDPR on the basis of our legitimate interests in target-oriented information of the users about us and our services as well as optimisation of our social media presence and effective communication with the users. If the respective social media providers ask the users for their consent to this processing of data (e.g. during registration by ticking a check box or by pressing a button), the legal basis of the processing is point (a) of Art. 6 (1) sentence 1 GDPR.Categories of Recipients of Data, Other Controllers, Data Transfers to a Third CountryService providers and agents engaged by us in connection with our social media presence, e.g. advertising agencies or IT service providers, may have access to the data mentioned in sections 2 and 3. Where these service providers and agents process data on our behalf, they are bound to instructions that we contractually impose on them.By contrast, the social media providers are not bound to any instructions, but process your data on their own responsibility. Information about the providers and their contact details can be found on their websites. There you will also find information about the processing of your personal data. Please note, that your data may be processed by the social media providers outside the territory of the European Union. This could result in risks for you, e.g. because this could make it more difficult for you to enforce your rights. More information on this subject is available from the respective social media providers.Your RightsYou can assert the following rights both towards us and towards the social media providers. If we do not have a particular piece of information that you request from us or are unable to fulfil your rights because we do not have access to your data, we will inform you accordingly in order to enable you to contact the respective providers.†Pursuant to Art. 15 GDPR, you have the right to obtain, free of charge, information about the personal data stored concerning you. Pursuant to Art. 16, 17 and 18 GDPR, you also have the right to rectification of inaccurate data as well as restriction of processing and erasure of your personal data.Under the conditions specified in Art. 20 GDPR, you also have the right to receive the stored data concerning you in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and to transmit those data to another controller without hindrance from us.Furthermore, pursuant to Art. 21 (1) GDPR, you have the right to object to the processing of personal data concerning you on the basis of point (e) or (f) of Art. 6 (1) sentence 1 GDPR, including profiling, on grounds relating to your particular situation. Where your personal data are processed for direct marketing processes, you have the right pursuant to Art. 21 (2) GDPR to object at any time to the processing of your data for such marketing, including profiling to the extent that it is related to such direct marketing.We will fulfil your aforesaid rights insofar as the statutory requirements for asserting the rights are on hand.Please submit all requests concerning your personal data to the respective social media provider or to the contact details specified at the beginning of this Privacy Policy.Moreover, every data subject has the right to lodge a complaint concerning our processing of data with a data protection supervisory authority.Duration of the Storage and Routine ErasureUnless specified otherwise for the specific data processing in this Privacy Policy, we only process and store personal data for the period required for the achievement of the purpose of the processing or to the extent provided for in laws or regulations that we are subject to.If the purpose of the storage no longer applies or a storage period required by law ends, the personal data will be routinely blocked or erased according to the statutory regulations.We may also store the data and information specified in sections 2 and 3 outside the social media. However, the aforesaid applies to the duration of the storage.NetiquetteWe look forward to a lively exchange on our social media channels.The basis for this, of course, is a polite atmosphere. We therefore ask you ñ in your interest and for the sake of other users ñ to be fair and respectful at all times. We reserve the right to delete posts found to be insulting or inappropriate, posts that contain advertising or offensive language or that have no relevance to our pages. If necessary, we will report and/or block users who violate our policies.†Please do not publish any illegal, banned or unauthorised content on our pages. HeidelbergCement assumes no responsibility and is not liable for content posted by users.Because our pages are publicly accessible, and because your privacy is important to us, we will delete any contributions that could potentially identify you or other persons (e.g. telephone number, address) without consent.
